Now it's time for the first of the off body tricks.
This trick is called the lasso.
I wonder why.
Yee-haw!.
It kind of feels and looks like you're a cowboy.
This is great move.
It's strengthens the arms.
It's nice and big, so you can clear space with it.
It's also one of the moves that you will move in and out of throughout your whole hooping routine.
You can turn with it.
You can kind of isolate it, spinning it around.
If you'd like to, you can even drop down on the floor and strike some hot pinup girl poses in it.
You can take your hands up in prayer.
You can do the right.
You can do the left.
You can even take it and isolate it somewhat holding it there.
Have a lot of fun with this move.
Lifting it up and away from the body.
Squatting down.
Make this move your own.
You ready to give it a try?